const Questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the National Day of Vietnam?",
    options: ["02/09/1940", "02/09/1945", "03/09/1975", "02/09/1946"],
    answer: "02/09/1945",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "In which year did the Dien Bien Phu victory take place?",
    options: ["1945", "1954", "1968", "1975"],
    answer: "1954",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "On which day did President Ho Chi Minh read the Declaration of Independence at Ba Dinh Square?",
    options: ["19/08/1945", "01/09/1945", "02/09/1945", "03/09/1945"],
    answer: "02/09/1945",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "In which year was the Paris Agreement on ending the war and restoring peace in Vietnam signed?",
    options: ["1954", "1968", "1973", "1975"],
    answer: "1973",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "On which day was the complete liberation of Southern Vietnam and national reunification?",
    options: ["19/08/1945", "30/04/1975", "02/09/1945", "20/07/1954"],
    answer: "30/04/1975",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "In which month of 1975 did the Ho Chi Minh Campaign begin?",
    options: ["March", "April", "May", "February"],
    answer: "April",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "In which year did Vietnam join the United Nations?",
    options: ["1975", "1977", "1986", "1995"],
    answer: "1977",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      'Which major battle ended the "Winter-Spring 1953-1954 Campaign"?',
    options: [
      "Border Campaign",
      "Northwest Campaign",
      "Dien Bien Phu Campaign",
      "Hue - Da Nang Campaign",
    ],
    answer: "Dien Bien Phu Campaign",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      'In which year did Vietnam officially change its name from "Democratic Republic of Vietnam" to "Socialist Republic of Vietnam"?',
    options: ["1975", "1976", "1977", "1980"],
    answer: "1976",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "When was the Communist Party of Vietnam founded?",
    options: ["02/09/1945", "03/02/1930", "30/04/1975", "07/05/1954"],
    answer: "03/02/1930",
  },
];

export default Questions;
